<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Suneo: Daily Earning App</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="questionmark">\??</string>

    <string name="landscape_warn">Pollfish is only shown in Portrait mode, except in tablets</string>
    <string name="survey_completed">Pollfish Survey Completed - Congratulations, you have won coins!</string>
    <string name="survey_offerwall_completed">Pollfish Survey Completed</string>
    <string name="logging">Logging area..</string>
    <string name="user_not_eligible">User Not Eligible</string>
    <string name="user_rejected_survey">User Rejected Survey</string>
    <string name="survey_not_available">Pollfish Survey Not Available</string>
    <string name="offerwall_available">Pollfish Offerwall available</string>
    <string name="survey_received">Pollfish Survey Received</string>
    <string name="on_pollfish_closed">onPollfishClosed</string>
    <string name="on_pollfish_opened">onPollfishOpened</string>

    <!--    ads-->
    <string name="adunit_reward">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/5224354917</string>
    <string name="app_open_ads">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/3419835294</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="termss"> <u>PRIVACY POLICY &amp; TERMS AND CONDITIONS </u> </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">

        <html>
<body>
<h2>Privacy Policy</h2>
<p> \n Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps)  built the Suneo: Daily Earning App an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) at no cost and is intended for use as is. </p>
<p>\n This page is used to inform website visitors regarding  my policies with the collection, use, and
    disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.</p>
<p>\n If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in
    relation with this policy. The Personal Information that  I collect are used for providing and
    improving the Service.  I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described
    in this Privacy Policy.</p>
<p>\n The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions,
    which is accessible at at Suneo: Daily Earning App , unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.</p>

<p><strong>Information Collection and Use</strong></p>
<p>\n For a better experience while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain
    personally identifiable information, including but not limited to name, email, phone number, internet, storage.
	The information that I request  will be retained on your device and is not
    collected by me in any way . The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.. </p>
<p>\n  Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app
•	Google Play Services
•	Google Analytics for Firebase
•	Firebase Crashlytics
    •	Unity  </p>


<p><strong>\n Log Data</strong></p>
<p> I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in case of an error in the app , I collect
    data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data
    may include information such as your devices’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name,
    operating system version, configuration of the app when utilising my Service, the time and date
    of your use of the Service, and other statistics.</p>

<p><strong>\n Cookies</strong></p>
<p>Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier.
    These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your devices’s
    internal memory.</p>
<p>>\n This Services does not uses these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code
    and libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to improve their services. You
    have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent
    to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of
    this Service.</p>

<p><strong>\n Service Providers</strong></p>
<p>I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:</p>
<ul>
    <li>To facilitate our Service;</li>
    <li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li>
    <li>To perform Service-related services; or</li>
    <li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li>
</ul>
<p>\n I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal
    Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they
    are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.</p>

<p><strong>\n Security</strong></p>
<p>/n I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use
    commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over
    the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot
    guarantee its absolute security.</p>

<p><strong>\n Links to Other Sites</strong></p>
<p>This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be
    directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I
    strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over, and
    assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party
    sites or services.</p>

<p><strong>\n Children’s Privacy</strong></p>
<p>This Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I  do not knowingly collect personal
    identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13
    has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you
    are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal
    information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.</p>

<p><strong>\n Changes to This Privacy Policy</strong></p>
<p>I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
    periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy
    on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
This policy is effective as of 2021-11-09 (9 november 2021). </p>

<p><strong>\n \n Contact Us</strong></p>
<p>If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact
me at unwiringapps@gmail.com or foundertanmay@gmail.com or you can contact me on telegram - @unwiringapps

</p>

    <br><br><br><br><p> <strong> \n \n Terms &amp; Conditions </strong> </p> </br></br></br></br>
<p>By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps).
Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
The Suneo: Daily Earning App app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, in order to provide my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the Suneo: Daily Earning App app won’t work properly or at all.
The app does use third party services that declare their own Terms and Conditions. </p>
<p>\n \n Link to Terms and Conditions of third party service providers used by the app
•	Google Play Services
•	Google Analytics for Firebase
•	Firebase Crashlytics
•	Unity </p>
<p> \n \n You should be aware that there are certain things that Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.
If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
Along the same lines, Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) cannot accept responsibility.
With respect to Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps)’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Tanmay Agarwal (Unwiring Apps) does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.
Changes to This Terms and Conditions
I may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.
These terms and conditions are effective as of 2021-11-09 (9 november 2021) </p>
<p> Contact Us </p>
<p> \n \n If you have any questions or suggestions about my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact me at unwiringapps@gmail.com or foundertanmay@gmail.com or you can contact me on telegram - @unwiringapps

</p>

</body>
</html>


</string>
    <string name="talksss">Hello Fam, I am Tanmay Agarwal from India. <br> \n\nI hope you love this Suneo Daily Earning App. \n\nI will be adding more interesting tasks in this app like interesting games, tic tac toe, and many more stuff in future updates.</br>  <p>  \n\n Note:- If users from countries like India, nepal , bangladesh, pakistan, and other countries facing the issue of no ads coming so i suggest you to use free American Vpn as sometimes unity ads filling rate is less in few countries  \n\n\n \nI tried my level best to make this app more useful for you all, so that you can regularly earn using this app, \nI have increase the earning in this app as compared to all the other earning apps available on playstore. </p>  \nIf you face any problems, or if sometimes any bug issue \n or \nif i forget to transfer any single money to you (even after 72 hours of withdraw time) then feel free to message me on telegram OR whatsapp, \nI will try my best to reply to every message and try to solve all possible issues. [Note:- Please message me only for the reasons mentioned here, please do not spam me for increasing coins or other unnecessary talks]  <br> \n \n If you like my work, please consider sharing this app with your friends and also please rate my apps on playstore, it helps me to stay motivated and make awesome apps for you all lovely peoples out there. \n \n Thank-you so much once again for your awesome support. </br> <p>\n \nIf you have any doubts, suggestions, questions, ideas, or want to convert your idea into a real android apps(ordering android apps) , feel free to message me on whatsapp +91 6395962636 \n\n or message me on my telegram @unwiringapps </p>, <p> Thank-you. </p> </string>
    <string name="withdrawl_note">Minimum withdraw \n1000 coins = 10 rupees \nafter Successful withdraw it take maximum 72 hours to transfer you \n\n \n note:- your account registered phone no. must be same as your paytm no. or google pay. \n \nIf not then no worries, kindly message me on whatsapp (+91 6395962636) or telegram (unwiringapps) with ur paypal, paytm, google pay details or bank details or you can send me your other payment methods details or crypto details if you want payment in other methods, after clicking on withdraw with screenshot mandatory as a proof of withdraw. \n\nSecondly i will send the full amount which you earn , so any sort of deduction is from paypal side, not from my side \n so i suggest to take your payment in crypto as there is no issue of money deduction\n\n\nif you have any suggestions or feedback message me on telegram (@unwiringapps) or \n\nyou can also join my telegram page of unwiring apps for more future earning apps and other useful updates. \nTelegram page username- @unwiringappspage1 or suneoapp page - @suneoapp \n\nfor any doubts or help \n message me on whatsapp +91 6395962636 \n\n or telegram - unwiringapps \n\n ONE REQUEST TO MY USERS - many people give bad feedback and rate low when the withdraw is delayed or other bugs, see guyz android apps requires a lot of efforts and hardwork and time but due to your 1 bad review our hardwork completely goes in vain, so i request you all if you face any bugs or issues or if sometime payment is delayed due to any reason, please try to ping me on my whatsapp or telegram so that i can resolve your problem asap, please - \nThank-You.\n\n Regards \n\nTanmay Agarwal</string>

</resources>